Ross, when's this
comet thing start?
Well, technically,
it started seven
billion years ago...
No, no!
Whoa!
Okay, okay,
fine, I'll stop.
No teaching, okay?
We'll just watch
the pretty lights
streaking across the sky.
Okay?
Okay.
Whose official name
is Bapstein-King...
Oh, come on!
Okay, okay!
There it is!
Oh, look at that.
Isn't Mother Nature amazing?
That's a plane.
Well, all right
1,700 bags of peanuts
flying that high
that's pretty amazing, too.
Hey, I wonder if you can see
my apartment from up here.
Oh, no, you can't.
What?
I don't... I don't know.
Wow, look at
all those stars.
Infinite space.
Really... really makes
you wonder, doesn't it?
Yeah.
You know what else
makes you wonder?
Huh?
Check out the rack
on this chick!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, we've been out here
for two hours
and we haven't seen
any stupid comets.
Can we go now?
I mean, Chandler's
getting chilly.
No, I'm n-not.
Then why are you wearing
Monica's jacket?
Because it's flattering.
Come on, Monica,
come on, Monica.
Yeah, you
know what?
I think we're going to take off.
We rented a movie.
Oh, I won't say no to a movie.
Oh, Pheebs, we just actually
kind of wanted to be alone.
Shh. Get me out of here.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Ross...
What?
Come here, check this out.
What, is it the comet?
No, no... look,
there's a bug stuck
in tar right here.
Joey, I can't believe it.
I bring you here to see
the Bapstein-King Comet
one of nature's most
spectacular phenomena
and all you care about
are bugs stuck in tar
and some woman.
You know,
there's two women, dude.
Show me where?
Right up here.
Joey, where's the pipe
that was holding
the door open?
I don't know.
Yeah, I do.
Joey!
What? All right...
Hey, don't look at me.
You're the one who
wanted to come up here
and look for some stupid...
Burger King Comet!
It's called
the Bapstein-King Comet, okay?
Oh...
Hey, hey!
Bapstein was a very
well-respected astronomer...
No-no! No!
No!
( whispering ):
Monica...
She's sleeping.
I know, just quick question.
Quick question.
Which one was
Deep Impact
and which one
was Armageddon?
Deep Impact was the one
with Robert Duvall.
Armageddon is what's
going to happen to you
if you wake me up.
Sorry, I just...
can't sleep.
Ooh!
( groans )
Where is that book
that you were reading
with the two women
who were ice-skating
and wearing those hats
with the flowers on it?
Because every time I look
at that cover, I'm like...
( snoring noises )
It is in the living room,
where there is also a light.
And no one will kick you
in the shin.
What?
Ow!
( beeping )
Please don't be a spaceship.
( beeping continues )
Oh, thank God.
( beeping )
( grunts )
How could you be beeping?
I just disconnected you!
I took out your battery!
( beeps )
How can--
Don't interrupt me!
Rachel!
Monica!
Come on!
I can't believe this!
All right, well, you know.
I guess we know what we
have to do to get down.
Yeah...
I guess we don't have a choice.
Help us!
Please, help us!
We're stuck up on the roof
and we can't get down!
Ross...
I was thinking we'd just go down
the fire escape.
I know, I wasn't finished.
But don't worry!
We're going to go down
the fire escape!
( loud clattering )
Shh!
I'm sorry. I thought maybe
I'd make some warm milk
and it would help me sleep.
With a wok?
I thought you were going to read
my boring book
to put you to sleep?
It got interesting.
Damn you, Oprah!
Here, let me
make the milk.
I'm up anyway.
Hey, you know
what we could do,
you know, now
that we're up?
We could just, like,
talk to each other
all night long.
You know, like we did
when we were first going out.
It'd be fun.
Okay, that does sound fun.
Yeah.
So, how bummed were you
when the second sister died,
huh?
The second sister dies?!
No...
No, I-I was, I was talking
about the book I was reading.
The second sister dies
in Archie and Jughead
Double Digest?
That's correct.
You want to go
in the bedroom?
A little more
comfortable.
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, wait, um...
Did you send those
contracts to Milan?
If this is your idea
of sexy talk...
( chuckles )
No, seriously.
You know the contracts
I gave you?
did you overnight them?
What contracts?
Okay, please tell me this
is just one of your jokes
that you do
that I don't get.
Like what?
You know, like the thing
when you put the phone
in your pants?
( laughs )
Tag, I'm serious.
This isn't funny.
Those contracts absolutely
had to go out today.
Rach, I'm sorry, but you
didn't give me any contracts.
Yes, I did and I put
a little Post-it on it
that said, "Must go out today"
and I underlined
"today" three times
and then I put a little heart
in the corner
'cause I didn't want to seem
too bossy.
I'm telling you,
you never gave them to me.
You know what, Tag,
if we went down to the office
you would see those contracts
sitting on your desk.
No, I would see you
looking embarrassed
because they are not on my desk.
Or maybe you would see me
looking embarrassed
because you are talking
on the phone with your crotch.
Look, do you want to go down
to the office right now?
No, come on, it's late.
We're not going to go down
to the office.
Yeah, I understand.
I wouldn't want
to be proved wrong either.
All right,
get your coat!
Oh! When did you unhook this?
Nice work.
( grunting )
It won't go down
any further, it's stuck.
( sighs )
Well, we're just
going to have to jump.
Yeah.
Now, we're going to
have to make sure
to land to the right
of that patch of ice, okay?
Not hit the Dumpster
on the other side
and try to avoid
that-that...
weird brownish-red
stuff in the middle.
So, when you
get down there...
you go up to the roof
and you let me in.
Whoa, wait a minute,
I have to do it?
Yeah, oh, yeah.
You'll be fine.
It'll be, uh...
just like bungee
jumping, you know?
But instead of
bouncing back up
you... you won't.
But what if I smack my head
on the concrete?
Well, I'm not going
to lie to you, Joey.
It's a possibility.
I don't know, Ross.
I tell you what
let's flip to see
who does it, okay?
You call it in the air,
all right?
Oh, all right.
Tails...
Ooh!
Can you... can you
see what it is?
No.
Okay, well, you
be careful.
Wha... no-no, Ross.
No, no... stop.
I'm not jumping!
Well...
Okay, look, I have
an audition tomorrow
and I can't go
if I break my leg.
Well, I'm not jumping.
I have a son, okay?
He won't have a
father if I die.
Well, all right,
so it looks like we're even.
Okay, so this wire
is connected to this wire
which plugs into here.
Okay, so to get the beeping
to stop,
all I have to do...
Well done, Pheebs.
( rapid beeping )
What do you want from me?!
Okay, here's your milk.
What do you want to talk about?
( slams door )
What? What?
Oh, were you sleeping,
sweetie?
I'm sorry... here.
Okay, feel free to look,
but I'm telling you
those contracts
are not on this desk.
How could you possibly know?
Look at this mess, Tag.
I mean, this is what
I'm talking about.
You have to be
more organized.
You've got newspapers,
you've got magazines,
you've... oh!
And who's this chippy?
A little young for you, Tag,
but whatever.
It's my sister?
Really? Very cute braces.
Anyway,
you know what?
The point is, Tag, start looking
because you are going to find
those contracts on your desk.
So when do
you imagine
you gave them to me?
In the morning
or in the afternoon?
In the afternoon.
Mr. Zelner came into my office
after lunch
he put them on my desk
and then I put a Post-it
on it...
that said...
"Must go out today."
So you just keep looking
in there, all right?
They're not here.
Puzzler.
Bit of a puzzle.
Why don't you, um, check
the copy room?
Maybe you left the contracts
in there.
How could I have left them
in the copy room?
I don't know, Tag-- how can your
genitals make phone calls?
Okay, it's not
a perfect world.
Just go, please.
Fine.
Thank you.
Hello.
I still don't get it.
You still awake?
Yeah. You?
You do know that was me
that just said that, right?
Hey, as long as
we're both up...
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
I hope you're not
thinking about
cleaning the living room.
Man, I'm starving.
What the hell was
I thinking at dinner--
"Do you want soup
or salad?"
Both. Always order both.
You know, you know,
I'm looking...
and I don't think
anyone's home here.
I say we just break
the window, crawl through,
and-and, you know,
explain later.
Really? No one's home?
I don't think so.
Hello?
( pounding )
( dog growling and barking )
So, when you get
in there...
( beeping )
Okay, this is where
you and I part ways...
Noisy bitch.
Oh... what?
What are you doing?
Do you know what
just happened?
Yeah. We-we had sex,
then we fell asleep.
No, we were in
the middle of sex...
and you fell asleep.
No...
No, that's not true.
No, best time ever.
Yeah, you rocked my world.
Monica?
What?
I was giving you some
of my best moves
and you missed it
so please wake up
so we can do it right.
Okay, okay, I'm ready.
Come on, big fella.
Okay...
Give me the good stuff.
Yeah!
No, no, no,
don't fall asleep.
Oh...
Okay, I am going to
make you some coffee.
Uh, I probably won't spill
coffee grounds
all over the kitchen floor.
Okay, I'm up, I'm up.
Hi.
I got you some coffee.
Two, uh...
So, do you got anything
for me?
Still no luck.
Oh, my God!
Did you check your entire desk?
Did you check all the drawers?
You want me to check again?
Well, yeah, I wish you would.
Well, no, it's not in there.
How about that drawer?
Well, it's not out here.
Is there any chance
it could be in your office?
I don't... I don't know.
Let me... let me check.
Any luck?
Tag, can I see you in my office
for a minute?
Yeah?
You found them!
You know what?
I'm not even going to gloat.
I'm just really relieved
this whole thing is over.
You put these on my desk.
I did not.
Oh, really?
So you're saying
they just slid
out of your bottom drawer,
crawled across the floor,
then jumped onto my desk?
How did you know
they were in my bottom drawer?
I am so hot for you right now.
( knocking )
( extended beeping )
Oh, my God!
How did you get back here?!
Man:
Phoebe Buffay?
( beeping continues )
Fire Alarm?
Oh, hi, Officer Fireman.
Can-can I help you?
We found your fire alarm
in the trash chute.
Mmm-hmm, that's not mine.
Yes, it is.
How do you know?
The next time you want to dump
a fire alarm in the trash cute,
don't wrap it in a blanket
that says
"Property of Phoebe Buffay,
not Monica."
Okay, do you...
Okay, do you have
a search warrant?
Because the last time
I checked,
this was still America.
Please reattach this.
It's against the law
to disconnect them.
Fine. But please,
God, tell me
how to stop it
from going off.
Press the reset button
under the plastic cover.
There's a reset button?
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Oh, there's a reset button!
My God! why didn't I see that?
Reset button, reset button...
Where is there a reset button?
Oh, here it is.
Oh!
Oh...
God!
Okay, you... you have
a good grip?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna start
to climb down you now.
All right, just hurry up.
Okay.
Now-now-now, should
I climb down your front
so we're face-to-face,
or should I climb down
your back, so we're... we're...
butt-to-face?
Face-to-face.
I think face-to-face, yeah.
Okay, here I come.
All right.
Oh, my... how much
do you weigh, Ross?!
I'd prefer not to answer that
right now.
I'm still carrying
a little holiday weight.
Uh...
( grunting )
Uh, you know, when we talked
about face-to-face,
I don't think we thought it
all the way through.
Well, what do you
want me to do?!
Just shimmy down me
and drop.
Oh!
Hi.
You know, m-maybe
I should hang
and you should
climb down me.
Yeah? Maybe we should talk
about that for a little while!
It still looks pretty far.
It's not that far.
Just drop.
Do not rush me!
Go!
( groaning )
Oh, Ross, you should know
that my pants are starting
to come down
and I'm not wearing any
underwear.
( screaming )
Oh! My ankle!
I really hurt my ankle!
I think I twisted it...
Ooh, a quarter!
That really was
some of your best work.
Mmm, I told you.
( snaps fingers )
Wow, I can't believe it,
I've only got two hours
until I call in sick for work.
I have to be up
in seven minutes.
Well, you're not gonna
to believe this,
but if you have
seven minutes...
Really?
You wanna?
Okay! You get
the vacuum cleaner
and I'll get
the furniture polish!